<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Services on Gabriela Kaszuba • Terapeuta</title>
    <link>https://gabrielakaszuba.pl/services/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Services on Gabriela Kaszuba • Terapeuta</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>pl-pl</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 15:15:26 +1000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://gabrielakaszuba.pl/services/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Accounting</title>
      <link>https://gabrielakaszuba.pl/services/accounting/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2018 12:33:46 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gabrielakaszuba.pl/services/accounting/</guid>
      <description>Financial accounting (or financial accountancy) is the field of accounting concerned with the summary, analysis and reporting of financial transactions related to a business.
Objectives Financial accounting and financial reporting are often used as synonyms.
 According to International Financial Reporting Standards: the objective of financial reporting is: To provide financial information that is useful to existing and potential investors, lenders and other creditors in making decisions about providing resources to the reporting entity.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Business Sales</title>
      <link>https://gabrielakaszuba.pl/services/business-sales/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 15:15:26 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gabrielakaszuba.pl/services/business-sales/</guid>
      <description>Cyanee nec pedicis positi. Esse et diem forte quoque et ieiunia vixque dixit negari ullis stamina: trahit. Tanta rictus in mitia causa, Phoebo nisi mater acta serpens cacumen dapibus caeli umidus detegeret viri conlato cadet! Ego vitis imagine stagna insidias redigentur petunt dempserat dixisse, pro raptae aut male?
 Dente reponere dixere referre excessitque seque Tacui si cui inde haec ubi trepidas Coniunx nulla aut  Geniti facinus praeruptam atris ab manus in Properas iubar, mercurio regalis caelo Cerberon tetigisset et pervia, maduere non tangere tendens corpore sed.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
